Sean Chambers

26th June 1995

117 Addison rd RD1 Onerahi Whangarei New Zealand 094365653 (Home) 021 103 9870 (Mobile) smchambers95@gmail.com

My name is Sean Chambers and I am 21 years of age. I am currently in my third year at AUT doing a Bachelor of Computer and Information Sciences. I am a responsible and confident person with the ability to relate to people of all ages. I am an organised and dedicated employee, with strong time management skills. I have great people/social skills and am at ease when it comes to interacting with clients, customers and fellow employees. I am thorough and vigilant in my duties appointed to me by my employer and am very willing and able to learn. With my positive attitude, enthusiasm and work history I feel I have much to offer a prospective employer.

Attributes and skills

- JAVA
- C++
- HTML
- PHP
- CSS
- Reliable
- Hardworking
- Good communication and listening skills
- Motivated
- Adaptable and flexible
- Enthusiastic and co-operative
- Motivate others
- Honest

Education

Tauraroa Area School 2003 – 2011 (Year 3 – Year 11) Whangarei Boys High School 2012 (Year 12) Auckland University of Technology (2014 – Current)

NCEA Level 2 BCIS Year 1, Year 2, & ½ Year 3 papers.

Employment History

Dick Smith – Electronics Store

November 2014 – November 2015

Position: Sales Manager

My duties in this role include;

- Opening/closing store responsibility
- Managing and working in a team of people
- Customer service and support

Bayfield's Agriculture LTD – Dairy Farm

December 2012 – February 2014

Position: Farm hand

My duties in this role included;

- Milking cows
- Sole responsibility for a herd
- Tractor driving
- General farming duties

Orion Health: Software Test Engineer

Dec 2015 (2 Weeks)

Position: Intern

My duties in this role included;

- User acceptance testing
- Error reporting

References

Work reference: Dick Smith NZ

Store manager – Timothy Ross –

021 083 85231

Work reference: Bayfield's Agriculture LTD

Manager- Karl Phillips – 021 243 7977

Work reference: Orion Health

Global Organisational Development Manager -

Emma Kirkman – 021 427 862